How do you feel about Senpai?
This is gonna make me sound like an otaku,
but he's kind of like Ashford-sama!
Doesn't that basically mean you're into him?!
Huh?
They went to that event together last weekend...
If Ririsa has a thing for Senpai,
that event would've been
the perfect opportunity...
Senpai, I love you...
Ririsa...
No, no way that'd happen. Not with Ririsa.
Stop worrying, Mikari!
Ririsa can try,
but Senpai will see that
I'm the better choice...
Okay!
Senpai, guess who's here!
Tips From a Master!?
Darn, it's just Ririsa.
You seriously need to lock the door.
Mikari-chan!
Thank you so much for your help!
I washed the clothes you lent me, here!
Put some on, first!
Oh, right.
So how did it go?
You better not have had any soft
moments with Senpai at that event!
We had a ton of fun.
After you asked me how I felt about him,
I started thinking about it more.
And I realized that I do love him,
as a supportive photographer and a friend!
Oh, I get it now. She's an idiot.
So, no changes.
Thank god both she and that
Lilliel lunatic are total morons.
That means I've still got a chance at him!
Where's Senpai, anyway?
The second-years had a test today,
so he'll be a little late.
I figured I could use this time to
get changed for today's shoot.
Uh-huh.
Class 1-1, Ririsa Amano!
Get to your classroom immediately!
I forgot about mandatory tutoring!
Maybe you should stop sleeping through class.
Mikari-chan, m-my stuff!
Will you watch my stuff?!
What?!
Thank you so much!
I didn't say I was gonna!
I've got other stuff to do, you know...
Why is my classroom so far
away from the club building?!
Watch out!
Ow...
I-I-I'm so sorry!
Are you okay?
You shouldn't be running in the halls.
Us girls have to be careful.
We don't want cuts or bruises ruining our good looks.
R-right, I'll be more careful, thanks!
T-that teacher was so pretty!
Sorry, Ririsa, that took longer than I thought.
It's not what you think, Senpai!
I thought if I dressed up as Lilliel
I might be able to understand you a little better?
Or like, if I were Lilliel,
maybe you'd like me a little bit more...
I'll take it off. I know it looks weird on me.
No, it, uh...
It's working?!
Guess he doesn't care who's wearing the costume!
Wait, then that proves he's not into Ririsa,
he's only into Lilliel...
Well, okay then!
Now's my chance!
Ashford-sama!
Lilliel! All up on me! What the hell?!
I-it's too much to bear!
I-I'm losing my mind!
Ashford-sama, I'm feeling a little different today...
So you can do whatever you want to me.
Whatever I want?!
Like...
Touch me...
wherever you want.
Touch you wherever I want?!
What now, Senpai?!
You can't say no to Lilliel, can you?!
I...
I can't.
Why not?
Lilliel might be my waifu,
but she's other people's waifu, too!
It wouldn't be okay for me to cross that line with her!
Darn.
It was worth a shot.
Stupid as that reaction was,
I do like how he's such a gentleman.
Still...
I wish he'd feel that way for me.
I'm so sorry I'm late! Let's get s...
W-wait, Ririsa!
Yeah, it's not what you think!
I'm seeing Lilliel in the flesh!
You're so cute and perfect!
D-don't make fun of me!
I know this looks dumb on me!
And I don't look like her at all.
My chest's too small, anyway.
That's not true!
Huh?
I did say you'd make a much better Miriella,
but I don't think you make a bad Lilliel!
You can cosplay whatever you want!
That's the great thing about cosplay:
anyone can be whatever character they want to be!
Really?
I totally agree, Mikari.
Fan art isn't about being accurate or correct.
Hell, 'bad' fan art is totally valid.
What's important is conveying
your love and having it understood.
That's what makes us happy.
Ririsa... Senpai...
You guys are way too naïve.
feeling guilty that she’s in
this for ulterior motives
So... What're you wearing under her skirt?
Whoa, those are intense panties!
How are they intense?!
Let me get a better look!
No! Okay, I'm sorry!
I'm never wearing this costume again!
Okumura, my lord!
Ogino-san!
T-thanks for having me today.
And sorry to text you out of the blue.
'Tis my pleasure!
I want to improve my skills before the next event.
I figured I could learn a few things from watching you.
I see!
You've come to me,
seeking a master from whom to train!
Did you perhaps sense my spirit has
been hardened by many a battle?
Indeed, it has!
I asked 'cause he's the only one I know...
Better not tell him.
Right, then, let us be off!
Y-yes, thanks again!
It's so easy to forget he's a nice guy...
Her costume today is very Japanese,
so we've rented out a traditional tatami room!
An environment perfectly suited for
the character is pivotal for a good photo.
W-whoa!
And if you want to sell lots of copies,
you must take photos in a proper studio!
With the cosplay scene continuing to grow,
rentable studios are all the more common,
and you can rent them for even cheaper on weekdays!
Ogino, is my obi okay in the back?
This costume is really high quality,
but once it's on I can't reach around to the back.
At once, milady!
That's Lady Folosso's oiran outfit!
That design literally just came out!
Okumura-kun, right? Hey! Good to see you.
Thanks for letting me sit in!
Hey, you're welcome.
A youngin' like you gets me inspired to work hard.
Are you not a college student yourself, milady?
L-let us begin, then!
There are two fundamental basics to remember:
timing and focus.
No amount of editing can fix a photo
that was poorly timed or is out of focus!
My next tip is to carefully consider
the theme of each photo you're taking.
What do you mean?
You aren't just capturing her expression or her posture.
Remain conscious of what you want to show the viewer.
Our job is to know what the cosplayer wants
and how they will time their expressions,
then capture both of those perfectly on film!
Let's begin!
Okey dokey!
First, keep your eye on our model,
and try to time your photo perfectly!
O-okay!
Hmm... novice.
Don't be annoyed!
This is why I asked him to help!
Compare your photo to mine now.
Okay.
Can you see how my shot was taken at
a slightly different moment than yours?
No two photographers are the same.
A good photo is a collaborative effort!
G-got it!
Okumura, milord!
Focus now on Lady Magino's breathing!
O-okay!
Then plan out how you will frame the shot!
Make it feel alive!
Lemme see!
Whoa, these are great!
You've totally got a knack for this.
H-he learns fast!
Perhaps because he had a most excellent teacher.
They look just like yours, Ogino!
Send this one to me,
I wanna put it on my next cosrom.
S-sure!
Now, then.
Is it okay if we start taking some sexier pics?
Yeah, sure, but... Are you okay with that?
Oh, yeah. Don't go getting a nosebleed on me.
Whatever is the matter?
I-it just feels weird to be taking these kinds of pictures.
Like, I feel like if I were her, I wouldn't want this.
While I can understand where you're coming from...
Do understand that cosplayers
enjoy when others look upon them.
We are here to help them achieve that.
What we are doing isn't wrong in the slightest!
Wait, Okumura-kun, do you have a crush on Lilliel-chan?
I can get why this would be weird.
No, that's not it!
I think Ogino-san's got the right idea about all this!
I just don't get why I can't think like that!
Then talk about it!
It's not okay to keep going if you're
keeping all that bottled up inside!
If something feels off,
then open up about it and argue if you have to!
That's how you strengthen
your relationships with people!
G-got it!
I'm really sorry for all this trouble.
You literally only met me once, and now...
Oh, c'mon, Okumura-kun!
Who cares if we've only met once?!
We tabled next to each other at an event!
That basically makes us friends!
Got it?
Y-you're sure?
Of course, my lord Okumura!
I'm in your debt, after all!
You have no idea how exciting
it was to discover Lilliel-chan.
Us photographers are always
wondering who will be next.
Next to what?
Okumura, perhaps a lesson is in order?
There are four women who stand
atop all others in the cosplay world.
We call them the Four Heavenly Queens of Cosplay!
The Four Heavenly Queens of Cosplay?!
The quiet, serious beauty who perfectly nails
the height and weight of every character,
Erika Awayuki!
The adorable cutie hired by big companies
to flaunt her perfect costumes and makeup,
Nagomi!
The tights-loving, fetish-feeding,
ultra-viral star with a rabid following,
Yoki Hoshizuki!
And the legendary goddess with a perfect
body and undying love for every character,
Mayura!
Together, they are the
Four Heavenly Queens of Cosplay!
There are way more than just four
incredible cosplayers out there,
but otaku love naming their "Three Musketeers"
or "Four Heavenly Lords," so.
Wait, but didn't Mayura retire?
My, you're quite with the times, then!
Indeed.
After last summer Comiket,
Mayura has not appeared at events
nor posted on social media.
As such, everyone wants to
know who will succeed her.
Who will claim her crown?!
And lo, as we wondered just that...
Your Lilliel came onto the scene.
Seeing her, I was reminded of the shock
I felt seeing Mayura for the first time...
And I tell you,
I was not the only one who felt that way.
W-wait, really?
So you see...
You see, I've invited you here today to assist our rival!
T'would be less exciting if she was burdened
by an inexperienced photographer!
I vow to take Lady Magino
to the top of the cosplay world!
What do you say to that, milord Okumura?!
I'm not that interested in being the best there is...
But, I'll admit... If you'll take me there,
I'm happy to come along.
Photography is a collaborative effort.
They're doing this together...
Okumura-senpai...
C'mon, Ririsa!
People kept calling me her partner,
and I didn't really get what that meant.
I thought Ririsa was the only one who mattered.
But I get it now. We do this together.
I promised I'd see things through to the finish line.
So if that's what Ririsa wants,
I'll take her there!
Ririsa? Is that her real name?
Aww! It's like she was born to play Lilliel!
Fear not. I will take that secret of hers to the grave.
In exchange, promise me you will
bring her to the next cosplay event!
We hope to see you guys there.
I will!
Okay, today wer'e talking about the
Aquarium Club's request for promotion.
161th Student Council Meeting
Aquarium Club Promotion Request
They’ve got six members and
Kotobuki-sensei as their advisor.
They’ve participated in a few contests,
and by all reports are doing quite well.
So they more than satisfy the
conditions for promotion to full club.
All those in favor?
Aye.
Can I see a raise of hands?
Wait, is it gonna be okay for them to
keep live animals in the club building?
Okay, that's a majority.
Then we need to send a notice
to the club getting demoted.
Senpai, what are these?!
I went shopping downtown this weekend.
Behold, my hard-earned spoils.
Can I look at them?!
Of course!
Lilliel
Wow, Senpai, these are intense...
But I suppose they're valuable
reference materials for sexier poses.
You don't even bat an eye, do you?
Is that Lilimaru's newest doujin?!
I love the way they draw Lilliel!
I love the way they do her eyes!
Lilliel’s Your Present
Prison Lilliel
Lilliel Bondage
You know, Senpai, are you more of a dom?
W-what makes you say that?!
I never really thought about it before!
I guess Lilliel doujins do have a lot of that stuff in it,
but I figured it's 'cause shonen manga girls
are always put into those kinds of situations.
Enough to change a man...
I totally get that!
It's supposed to be for kids,
but it's not all that innocent...
But since I self-insert as the female characters,
I guess that makes me more of a sub.
Sounds like we're a perfect match!
A perfect match?!
Ririsa
S-senpai...
Get that stupid image out of your head, idiot!
Y'know, it's even hotter when
she's in even more trouble...
You sure you're not more of a domme?
There are a lot of girl characters who
can get themselves out of trouble, too.
I love them, too!
But I'm all about Lilliel,
so my favorite is when the
hero comes rushing in to save her.
Right, should we start taking pictures?
Yes! And I've got an idea.
Let's take pictures of Lilliel in trouble!
L-Lord Ashford will come to rescue me, I know it!
She's so into this!
Carefully consider the theme of each photo you're taking.
Consider the theme... Right.
Maybe focus on her bound arms?
And get a shot looking down at her.
Could you turn around and face me?
Senpai! Is it me, or did you get so much better at this?!
So, uh...
You got some lessons from Magino-san's photographer?
Yeah, we had a little training session, I guess.
Sorry I didn't mention it before.
Senpai, you did this for me?
Ogino-san told me this isn't about us working separately.
We have to work together as a team.
If you want to be cosplay famous,
then I can't just be there for the ride.
I have to put in the work.
Is that something you want?
I-I'm just happy showing
everyone how much I love Lilliel.
I was never interested in getting famous,
or taking Mayura-sama's crown.
Oh. Okay, then.
But...
I've been happy just enjoying, making,
and wearing my cosplays by myself...
But going to that event with you,
and having so many people
see me in my Lilliel cosplay,
made me start to want more.
I mean, it was so much fun!
Wasn't it so much fun?!
I always wanted to go to cosplay events,
but I had no idea they were gonna be that fun.
Who knows how fun it'll feel to go to bigger events,
to be seen by even more people?
To be seen by even bigger crowds?
For them to know how much I love her...
Thank you, Senpai. I'd be on board for that idea.
Is it really okay for me to ask you to help me get there?
I promised I'd help with everything, didn't I?
Besides, I had fun, too.
Let's see just how far we can go together.
Yeah!
Manga Club
The photo studio we were at was crazy, too.
I don't think we can afford it just yet, though.
Wow! I've never been to one, either.
We can manage with just our club room
if we make some backdrops and props.
Yeah! I love our clubroom-
Student council. Is the club president here?
The student council?!
Unlock this door.
It's against school policy to have
the doors locked for no reason.
Lilliel, hide!
I-I'm coming!
Sorry to bother you.
What can I do for you?
Nothing, just a message for you.
As of today, the Aquarium Club
has been promoted to full club status.
Huh? The what club?
As such, the Manga Club will be demoted
from full club to meeting group.
Wait, what?! Why?!
According to our records,
the Manga Club has not
qualified for full status for three years.
It wasn't a problem before because
there were open club rooms.
For three whole years?
You're the club president. How did you not know?
In any case,
we're going to give this room to them instead.
We Need an Advisor!